<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Homepage on Root-Dynamics</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Homepage on Root-Dynamics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 15:15:26 +1000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloud Consulting</title>
      <link>/services/cloud_consultancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Apr 2021 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/cloud_consultancy/</guid>
      <description>Custom solutions architecting made to fit your business&amp;rsquo; unique needs. Specializing in Cloud native and multi-cloud solutions. Our Strata Root-Dynamics offers consulting on creating Cloud Solutions tailored to your business&amp;rsquo; needs. With an approach backed by Site Reliability Engineering fundamentals and a cost-centric focus, we provide best in class solutions.
Core Competencies The public cloud and it&amp;rsquo;s associated problem space are vast, to give an idea of what we can offer your business here are some brief points of interest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managed Solutions</title>
      <link>/services/managed_solutions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2021 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/managed_solutions/</guid>
      <description>Root Dynamics is a leading managed service provider for all your IT needs. We provide a range of services that are designed to make life easier for you.
Whether it&amp;rsquo;s just monitoring or we are managing your entire IT infrastructure, Root Dynamics provides the best quality service.
This way you can focus on running your business and not worry about any of the technology headaches.
With managed services, you get the peace of mind that everything on your network is being monitored 24/7.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Acquisitions</title>
      <link>/services/acquisitions/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/acquisitions/</guid>
      <description>Acquisitions in the field of information technology is concerned with the purchase and fulfillment, of hardware or software to meet a business&amp;rsquo; unique needs.
Knowing what to buy, who to buy it from, and how to handle licensing can quickly become overwhelming.
We are authorized resellers of:
Dell Lenovo Ubiquiti Cisco Hardware The three main options for the acquisitions of information technology equipment are
Buying Renting Leasing Each with its own set of considerations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Root Dynamics was founded on two principals.
1. The best solution is one that addresses the root of the problem.
2. An organization’s success is governed by the extent to which its technology strategy supports its business strategy.
Our Story Root Dynamics is a service disabled veteran owned small business that provides IT Consulting, Managed Services, Cloud consulting, and Security Consulting. We have experience in many industries to provide expertise in all environments.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>Our staff&amp;rsquo;s availability to best assess and provide for your unique business needs.
Day Opening Hours Monday 8:30am - 5:00pm Tuesday 8:30am - 5:00pm Wednesday 8:30am - 5:00pm Thursday 8:30am - 5:00pm Friday 8:30am - 5:00pm Saturday Closed Sunday Closed </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
